TROND KJETIL BREMNES

Kvenvikbakken 1, 9518 Alta, Norway (+47) 97120488 <u>tkbremnes@gmail.com</u> <u>http://trondkjetilbremnes.com</u>

STUDENT AT NORWEGIAN UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

Summary

Student of Informatics/Computer Science with programming experience in Java and agile programming methods. Interested in human-computer interaction and interface design, as well as web development. Currently studying for a Masters Degree in Human Computer Interaction at NTNU.

Skills

Java

• HTML + CSS

• Ruby on Rails

Education

Norges teknisk-naturvitenskapelige universitet (NTNU)

2011 - 2013

Masters, Human Computer Interaction

Norges teknisk-naturvitenskapelige universitet (NTNU)

2008 - 2011

Bachelor, Informatics

Member of Board of European Studens of Technology LBG Trondheim, member of the local student skeptic society

Handelshøyskolen BI Markedskandidat, Marketing 2006 - 2008

Experience

Gurutjenesten Guru 09 / 2009 - Present

Computer support for employees and students at Department of Computer and Information Science at NTNU.

Bouvet ASA Summer Intern 06 / 2011 - 07 / 2011

Built a web site tailored for mobile devices. Written in C# and Asp.net Web Forms, communicating with a Microsoft Sharepoint server via SP Web Services.

Languages

• Norwegian

• English